adskom.com 2015-05-08

# Data Collection Opt-Out & Privacy Policy | ADSKOM

Data Collection Opt-Out

We believe that delivering targeted and relevant advertising enhances your Internet experience. We collect non-personally identifiable information from many of the websites in which Adskom Platform is enabled, and use that information to deliver targeted advertising on those websites as well as other websites you may visit.

If you prefer that we do not collect non-personally identifiable information about your website visits for the purpose of delivering targeted advertising, you may opt out by clicking on the “opt-out” link below.

When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to use your information for delivering relevant online advertisements. Please note that if you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice. 

Privacy Policy

We collect certain non-personally identifiable information automatically for use on our platform (the “Adskom Platform” ). We enable our Publishers to use this information for online ad targeting as described below.

(a) The Information We Gather and How We Use It:

  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  — We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information on the Adskom Platform. For example, when you visit a web page that has Adskom Platform enabled, our server logs collect your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time you visited that web page, and (if you came to a web page via a search engine such as Google), the web search that landed you on that web page. We also collect information regarding how often you share content with others using the Adskom platform. We use this information to help us build commercially viable data segments (e.g., travel enthusiast, sports fan) for online ad targeting in order to help make the ads you see on many of the websites you visit more relevant to your interests, and for ad delivery and reporting purposes. We also set Cookies and web beacons on web pages where our Adskom Platform is enabled, and allow our partners to set Cookies and web beacons that are subject to those partners’ privacy statements. We also use this information to customize the Adskom Platform to your usage patterns.

(b) Information Sharing.

We share information collected via the Adskom Platform with other companies or individuals as follows:

  * We share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with partners and the website Publishers who have the Adskom Platform enabled on their websites for targeted advertising purposes and for identifying the top audience segments. Publishers may use this information to personalize the advertising on individual publisher sites.
  * We share any information with third parties if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or an enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Adskom Platform, the public as required or permitted by law.
  * We share information with our subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us, in which case we will require them to honor this policy. Additionally, in the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, we expect that any and all information that we have will be among the assets transferred.
  * In addition, we may aggregate your Non-Personally Identifiable Information with the Non-Personally Identifiable Information of others and share that aggregated information with third parties without restriction.

(c) Targeted Advertising and Choices

We set Cookies and web beacons on web pages where our Adskom Platform are enabled to help us with online ad targeting to our website Publishers.

If you prefer that we do not collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your website visits for the purpose of delivering targeted advertising, you may opt out at our Data Collection Opt-Out page.

When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to use your information for delivering relevant online advertisements. Please note that if you block cookies, our opt-out process may not function properly. Please also note that if you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.
